Contact

ersilia@nando1.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ersiliapompilio-rn-msn-pnp-84042752 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Pediatrics

PALS

Nursing

Languages

Italian (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Full Professional)

Publications

When Nurses Smoked In Hospitals
Our Little Hospital Ghost

The Most Haunted Hospital In America

Remember, nurses are human too Do TV Nurses Represent You?

Ersilia Pompilio RN, MSN, PNP

Public Speaker, Consultant, Writer, Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Burbank. California

Summary

Pediatric Nurse Practitioner extraordinaire with over 20 years of expert Pediatric experience. My expertise include: consulting, education, and creative endeavors. I am the CEO and owner of "The Well Written Nurse(TM)", "Nurses and Hypochondriacs Stroytelling Inc. (TM)(503c), and "Nurses and Hypochondriacs the podcast, and Comedic Lecture Series.

My goal is to EMPOWER NURSES from all disciplines to WRITE, tell their stories, and educate the general public about Health Care through creativity.

Expertise: creative educational products to fit the specific needs of clients.

Experience

Nurses and Hypochondriacs Inc. DBA Rogue Nurse Media 501c3 CEO, Producer

June 2015 - Present (5 years 2 months)

Burbank

Rogue Nurse Media 501c3 www.roguenursemedia.com

Mission: To Empower Nurses and Patients To Tell Their Stories

Live Storytelling Performances: Nurses, Patients and Hypochondriacs tell true unscripted stories.

Podcast: Discussion on HOT TOPICS in healthcare with Nurse Experts, Patients, and Hypochondriacs.. All Peer reviewed data ... Nurses get CE's for Listening and Watching our shows!

Nurses and Hypochondriacs storytelling Inc DBA Rogue Nurse Media is a (501)(3c)(TM) nonprofit.

The Well Written Nurse (TM)

CEO/ Owner

January 2016 - Present (4 years 7 months)

Burbank

Pompilio and Associates
Legal Nurse consultant/ Nursing Consultant
September 2007 - Present (12 years 11 months)
Burbank

Owner/ CEO: preform legal nurse consulting on medical malpractice cases, personal injury, expert witness services.

Publicis Touchpoint Solutions/ Astrazeneca Cardiology Clinical Nurse Consultant April 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 9 months) Glendale

Providing Education and educational resources to Nurses, Discharge planners and Pharmacists on the importance of oral anti platelet therapy for the ACS patient.

Charles R Drew University
Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Professor
September 2013 - March 2014 (7 months)
Willowbrook

Courses taught: Pediatric Physical Assessment, Pediatrics, Pediatric Clinical, Fundamentals of Nursing, Community Health Nursing, also provided counseling services for students, as well as served on various committees: Admissions and was vice Chair of Faculty Assembly that met once a week.

LAC + USC Pediatric Neurology
Pediatric Neurology Nurse Practitioner
June 2013 - September 2013 (4 months)

History and Physical exams, Neurology assessment and diagnosis. Case management duties in a team oriented environment. Inpatient and outpatient visits. CCS expertise.

Children's Hospital Los Angeles CHLA Pediatric Nurse Practitioner September 2007 - July 2013 (5 years 11 months)

Performed health histories and physical assessment's for the pediatric population. Departments: Anesthesia/ Radiology

CSUN

Nursing Clinical Professor January 2009 - January 2010 (1 year 1 month) Northridge

Pediatric Clinical Professor

UCLA School of Nursing
Pediatric Clinical Professor
June 2009 - September 2009 (4 months)

Pediatric clinical Professor

Mt. St. Mary's College Nursing Professor August 2007 - September 2008 (1 year 2 months)

Lecture: Nursing issues to senior student's.

Taught Clinical: Leadership and management

Taught Clinical: Nursing preceptorship

Counseling services to Junior level students

Pro Care One Registered Nurse September 1999 - September 2007 (8 years 1 month) Irvine, CA

Nursing Registry: Registered Nurse worked at over 30 hospitals in Los Angeles and Orange County area: specialty: Pediatrics, Pediatric ICU, NICU, Maternity/ Newborn Nursery

Citrus Valley Health Partners
Pediatric Nurse Practitioner
February 2006 - March 2007 (1 year 2 months)

Performed health histories/ Physical assessment's, with diagnosis and written prescriptions when necessary. Education to families and pediatric patient's.

Disneyland Resort Registered Nurse/ Disenyland Health Services October 1999 - July 2001 (1 year 10 months) Anaheim, CA

Registered Nurse @ Disneyland Health services for guests and employee's

Education

UCLA

Master of Nursing, Pediatric Nurse Practitioner · (2003 - 2005)

CSULB

BSN, Nursing · (1997 - 1999)

Pasadena City College

ADN, Nursing Science · (1991 - 1995)